<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>life on talentdmrripley</title>
    <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in life on talentdmrripley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 23:41:42 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://talentdmrripley.com/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Self Reject</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/dont-self-reject/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 23:41:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/dont-self-reject/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t self reject. It&amp;rsquo;s the best piece of advice I&amp;rsquo;ve heard in a long time.
That&amp;rsquo;s it. Apply for the job. Post the picture. Submit the article. Share the idea. Call the girl. Take a chance. That’s all.
Don’t self reject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Courage Always Wins</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/2012/courage-always-wins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 15:53:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/2012/courage-always-wins/</guid>
      <description>I have a little motto going: courage always wins. It&amp;rsquo;s about looking fear in the eye, not blinking.
Not knowing the outcome — not needing to. I own the last word; it belongs to me. Fear can&amp;rsquo;t leave unanswered questions; all the smudges on whichever lens I view the world.
Dared in that instant. Tried it. Wrote it. Said it. Walked in/out. Asked. Answered boldly. Fought for it.
Loved.
Success. Failure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Things I Learned From My Dog, Fletch: Part 3</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/random-things-i-learned-from-my-dog-fletch-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 17:47:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/random-things-i-learned-from-my-dog-fletch-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Take a walk, friend. Change it up. Move your paws, nose the ground. Run it &amp;lsquo;round and &amp;lsquo;round, like a Hoover vacuum, over and over and back again. Secrets dangle from the blades of grass, like shimmering drops of morning dew. Stop. Sniff out the stories. Draw in the odiferous. Write your own story in the prickly green. Share it. Life is not a journey to somewhere else. Wag instead in the wideness of now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hard Knocks</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/hard-knocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 17:51:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/hard-knocks/</guid>
      <description>Knock-knock-knock on the door. Fast knocks. Hard knocks. I&amp;rsquo;m busy, dammit. Was busy. Knock-knock-knock, heavier, faster. Coming. I&amp;rsquo;m coming, little shit. Eyes press against the narrow glass next to the door, framed by little hands, like the inside of my house some kind of show, or worse a circus. I see him. He sees me. Busted. He slides out of view, waits.
I open the door. I know how it goes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rashful Reminder</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/2012/rashful-reminder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2012 17:58:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/2012/rashful-reminder/</guid>
      <description>A rashful reminder remains from my stroke. The drug that saved my life (the me inside of me), tPA (tissue plasminogen activator, fancy for heavy duty clot-buster), didn&amp;rsquo;t take the first time. They shot it into my arm and they missed; the drug stayed there, though, festered under the skin and soggy like spilled milk under a newspaper. The trauma team eventually found purchase in a vein with another dose, though, sparing my brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Things I Learned From My Dog, Fletch: Part 2</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/random-things-i-learned-from-my-dog-fletch-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 18:07:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/random-things-i-learned-from-my-dog-fletch-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Dogs pee on things. A lot. And they like peeing on things, a lot. Fresh patches of grass and wall to wall carpeting present perfect places to piss. Add to that: street corners, bushes, pathways, sidewalks, fire hydrants, trees, park benches, swing sets, car tires, mailboxes, flagpoles, and flowers. Nothing on the ground is safe from a raised leg and urine to spare.
It&amp;rsquo;s much more than just a birthright. They&amp;rsquo;re programmed to mark territory, claim it as their own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Average</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/average/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 20:18:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/average/</guid>
      <description>I shot for average growing up and that’s what I got. School was no cake walk, but it wasn’t hard or anything. Learning bored me. Homework? What’s that? I got a lot of D’s on my progress reports, which sent my parents into the stratosphere over and over again. They threatened me within an inch of my life over and over, and I would rally across the finish line, and hold my hands up in victory for average, for a fucking C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take a Chance</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/2011/take-a-chance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2011 21:32:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/2011/take-a-chance/</guid>
      <description>How many chances does one get in life, as allotted by God, or the powers that be &amp;ndash; those unseen forces moving behind life like stagehands doing what the big director tells them? It stands to reason, if you spend any time reasoning within the confines of faith, that chances are predetermined, or fixed. ( **Feel free to attack this question from a non-religious angle. We&amp;rsquo;re all friends here.)
Chances don’t breed with other chances, they just exist until used up, or get missed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1,000 Miles of Optimism</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/2011/1000-miles-of-optimism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 21:40:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/2011/1000-miles-of-optimism/</guid>
      <description>Life seemed to be more fun when your life was out there somewhere, waiting in the future. It was mysterious and you would get to it eventually. Pieces would fit together like a happy puzzle of meaning and fulfillment.
From a thousand miles out the future looked perfect, or adequate at the very least. The perfect job would occupy your days with purpose, and the perfect spouse would occupy your nights with passion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Vixen Named Clarity</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/2011/a-vixen-named-clarity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 21:49:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/2011/a-vixen-named-clarity/</guid>
      <description>She is one of those words in bold print on the pages of your life story. Clarity. It means having the quality of being certain or definite. Clear. Her only purpose, as it relates to how we process the world around us, is to convey that this &amp;ndash; whatever this is &amp;ndash; is important.
Routine becomes vague; the path familiar; the pace: machine-like and automatic; the challenges many; the needs plenty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sack Up</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/2010/sack-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 21:57:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/2010/sack-up/</guid>
      <description>Too much nutsack or not enough. That&amp;rsquo;s it. Too much nutsack and the by-product of boldness, courage, and self assuredness always at the ready. Or not enough nutsack and the by-product of timidness, hesitation, and self doubt are the order of the day.
Simple things like speaking up in a crowd or a propensity for picking fights means you probably have a surplus in the nutsack department. By contrast, bolting from conflict, constanly caving to the wants of others, or shrinking like a violet in the face of almost anything can safely be assessed as having too little nutsack.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
