<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dogs on talentdmrripley</title>
    <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/tags/dogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dogs on talentdmrripley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 17:47:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://talentdmrripley.com/tags/dogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Random Things I Learned From My Dog, Fletch: Part 3</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/2012/random-things-i-learned-from-my-dog-fletch-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 17:47:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/2012/random-things-i-learned-from-my-dog-fletch-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Take a walk, friend. Change it up. Move your paws, nose the ground. Run it &amp;lsquo;round and &amp;lsquo;round, like a Hoover vacuum, over and over and back again. Secrets dangle from the blades of grass, like shimmering drops of morning dew. Stop. Sniff out the stories. Draw in the odiferous. Write your own story in the prickly green. Share it. Life is not a journey to somewhere else. Wag instead in the wideness of now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Things I Learned From My Dog, Fletch: Part 2</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/2012/random-things-i-learned-from-my-dog-fletch-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 18:07:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/2012/random-things-i-learned-from-my-dog-fletch-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Dogs pee on things. A lot. And they like peeing on things, a lot. Fresh patches of grass and wall to wall carpeting present perfect places to piss. Add to that: street corners, bushes, pathways, sidewalks, fire hydrants, trees, park benches, swing sets, car tires, mailboxes, flagpoles, and flowers. Nothing on the ground is safe from a raised leg and urine to spare.
It&amp;rsquo;s much more than just a birthright. They&amp;rsquo;re programmed to mark territory, claim it as their own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Things I Learned From My Dog, Fletch: Part 1</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/2012/random-things-i-learned-from-my-dog-fletch-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 18:13:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/2012/random-things-i-learned-from-my-dog-fletch-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Like all divorces, mine was hard on the family, especially my kids. We spent Christmas Eve together, then they were gone. Gone like Christmas. Nobody was ready for it, certainly not me.
Fletch picked a spot at the top of the stairs, overlooking the front door and entryway. He waited for days, head lowered, ears peeled. It was everything a picture of vigilance. Cars passed by the house, sending his head up off the floor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
