<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on talentdmrripley</title>
    <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on talentdmrripley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 22:30:56 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Soccer</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 16:25:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/soccer/</guid>
      <description>My new favorite sport is soccer, more commonly referred to worldwide as football. Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s a very un-American thing to do, actually like soccer. But I don&amp;rsquo;t care. The leagues are fascinating to follow. The players are from all over the world. There seems to be a more authentic level of diversity in the world of soccer. And I kind of like diversity lately. Call me crazy.
The teams I like are cities I&amp;rsquo;ve been to: Seattle Sounders FC, Manchester City, and Bayern Munich.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wfh One Year Later</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/wfh-one-year-later/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 23:36:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/wfh-one-year-later/</guid>
      <description>Roughly a year ago I started working from home because of COVID-19. There were lots of adjustments early on. I work in marketing so, really, I can perform that function anywhere with internet access.
METER Group, where I work, was able to stay open because it&amp;rsquo;s an essential business that helps food companies produce food. Production went to two shifts while most of the office staff shifted to wfh.
All in all, it&amp;rsquo;s been fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Self Reject</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/dont-self-reject/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 23:41:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/dont-self-reject/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t self reject. It&amp;rsquo;s the best piece of advice I&amp;rsquo;ve heard in a long time.
That&amp;rsquo;s it. Apply for the job. Post the picture. Submit the article. Share the idea. Call the girl. Take a chance. That’s all.
Don’t self reject.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
