<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on talentdmrripley</title>
    <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on talentdmrripley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 22:52:14 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>May Hot Things</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/may-hot-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 10:05:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/may-hot-things/</guid>
      <description>1. Grand entrance First, we welcomed our first grandchild, Lana Jane, into the family on May 18th. She&amp;rsquo;s a great baby so far and I really like holding her. Lana&amp;rsquo;s parents are doing a great job and it&amp;rsquo;s fun to watch them work together and love on their first child.
There&amp;rsquo;s something about when your babies have babies that you finally feel semi-successful as a parent. Is that true for anyone else?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April Hot Things</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/april_hot_things/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 17:32:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/april_hot_things/</guid>
      <description>So April 2021 has almost come to a close but here are the things asking for a fair bit of my attention this month. In no particular order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soccer</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 16:25:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/soccer/</guid>
      <description>My new favorite sport is soccer, more commonly referred to worldwide as football. Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s a very un-American thing to do, actually like soccer. But I don&amp;rsquo;t care. The leagues are fascinating to follow. The players are from all over the world. There seems to be a more authentic level of diversity in the world of soccer. And I kind of like diversity lately. Call me crazy.
The teams I like are cities I&amp;rsquo;ve been to: Seattle Sounders FC, Manchester City, and Bayern Munich.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wfh One Year Later</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/wfh-one-year-later/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 23:36:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/wfh-one-year-later/</guid>
      <description>Roughly a year ago I started working from home because of COVID-19. There were lots of adjustments early on. I work in marketing so, really, I can perform that function anywhere with internet access.
METER Group, where I work, was able to stay open because it&amp;rsquo;s an essential business that helps food companies produce food. Production went to two shifts while most of the office staff shifted to wfh.
All in all, it&amp;rsquo;s been fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Self Reject</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/dont-self-reject/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 23:41:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/dont-self-reject/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t self reject. It&amp;rsquo;s the best piece of advice I&amp;rsquo;ve heard in a long time.
That&amp;rsquo;s it. Apply for the job. Post the picture. Submit the article. Share the idea. Call the girl. Take a chance. That’s all.
Don’t self reject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Happy at Work</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/are-you-happy-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 16:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/are-you-happy-at-work/</guid>
      <description>Am I happy at my job? Does my career challenge me month after month? How does my job make me feel? These are just a few questions we ask ourselves as we navigate our careers.
Habit trackers are a cornerstone of Bullet Journaling. #BuJo users track all kinds of habits, mine being fairly simple: reading, working out, and work happiness.
How did I feel when I left work today? Work Happiness is a daily question and a score:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Company Culture</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/company-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 04:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/company-culture/</guid>
      <description>Culture comes down to how you feel about your company, and how your company feels about you.
A two-way lens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bullet Journaling: 7 Takeaways</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/bullet-journaling-7-takeaways/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 04:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/bullet-journaling-7-takeaways/</guid>
      <description>Back in January, I downloaded Ryder Carroll&amp;rsquo;s book, The Bullet Journal Method.
 For years, Ryder Carroll tried countless organizing systems, online and off, but none of them fit the way his mind worked. Out of sheer necessity, he developed a method called the Bullet Journal that helped him become consistently focused and effective.
 I decided to give Bullet Journaling a try. And while the book is straightforward with a great framework for getting started, you have to find your own way with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Things I Learned From My Dog, Fletch: Part 3</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/random-things-i-learned-from-my-dog-fletch-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 17:47:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/random-things-i-learned-from-my-dog-fletch-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Take a walk, friend. Change it up. Move your paws, nose the ground. Run it &amp;lsquo;round and &amp;lsquo;round, like a Hoover vacuum, over and over and back again. Secrets dangle from the blades of grass, like shimmering drops of morning dew. Stop. Sniff out the stories. Draw in the odiferous. Write your own story in the prickly green. Share it. Life is not a journey to somewhere else. Wag instead in the wideness of now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hard Knocks</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/hard-knocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 17:51:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/hard-knocks/</guid>
      <description>Knock-knock-knock on the door. Fast knocks. Hard knocks. I&amp;rsquo;m busy, dammit. Was busy. Knock-knock-knock, heavier, faster. Coming. I&amp;rsquo;m coming, little shit. Eyes press against the narrow glass next to the door, framed by little hands, like the inside of my house some kind of show, or worse a circus. I see him. He sees me. Busted. He slides out of view, waits.
I open the door. I know how it goes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Things I Learned From My Dog, Fletch: Part 2</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/random-things-i-learned-from-my-dog-fletch-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 18:07:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/random-things-i-learned-from-my-dog-fletch-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Dogs pee on things. A lot. And they like peeing on things, a lot. Fresh patches of grass and wall to wall carpeting present perfect places to piss. Add to that: street corners, bushes, pathways, sidewalks, fire hydrants, trees, park benches, swing sets, car tires, mailboxes, flagpoles, and flowers. Nothing on the ground is safe from a raised leg and urine to spare.
It&amp;rsquo;s much more than just a birthright. They&amp;rsquo;re programmed to mark territory, claim it as their own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Things I Learned From My Dog, Fletch: Part 1</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/random-things-i-learned-from-my-dog-fletch-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 18:13:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/random-things-i-learned-from-my-dog-fletch-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Like all divorces, mine was hard on the family, especially my kids. We spent Christmas Eve together, then they were gone. Gone like Christmas. Nobody was ready for it, certainly not me.
Fletch picked a spot at the top of the stairs, overlooking the front door and entryway. He waited for days, head lowered, ears peeled. It was everything a picture of vigilance. Cars passed by the house, sending his head up off the floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Average</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/average/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 20:18:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/posts/average/</guid>
      <description>I shot for average growing up and that’s what I got. School was no cake walk, but it wasn’t hard or anything. Learning bored me. Homework? What’s that? I got a lot of D’s on my progress reports, which sent my parents into the stratosphere over and over again. They threatened me within an inch of my life over and over, and I would rally across the finish line, and hold my hands up in victory for average, for a fucking C.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
