<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Archives on talentdmrripley</title>
    <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Archives on talentdmrripley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 15:50:51 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Birch Court</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/birch-court/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 15:50:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/birch-court/</guid>
      <description>Recurring dream: I&amp;rsquo;m in our old house, the one we moved out of 9 years ago. I&amp;rsquo;m panicked because the new owners have been waiting for us to move our things out. Our stuff and their stuff, miscellany, fills the house. At first they&amp;rsquo;re not home. I start making an inventory and wander through each room. The living room still has our hunter green plaid couch and matching love seat, oak entertainment center, coffee table, computer desk, and kids craft table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pimp Hand</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/pimp-hand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 12:14:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/pimp-hand/</guid>
      <description>Big Raunch sold tricks and Candy was his best seller. He lurked in the shadows, keeping an eye on his prized mule. It was 2 AM in the city. A fresh rain bathed the streets, but not enough to douse the rotten stench bouquet of trash and shit and piss and booze and vomit.
Big Raunch poached somebody else’s turf, so he and Candy had to slink back a ways, set up shop off the main drag, so to speak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Courage Always Wins</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/courage-always-wins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 15:53:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/courage-always-wins/</guid>
      <description>I have a little motto going: courage always wins. It&amp;rsquo;s about looking fear in the eye, not blinking.
Not knowing the outcome — not needing to. I own the last word; it belongs to me. Fear can&amp;rsquo;t leave unanswered questions; all the smudges on whichever lens I view the world.
Dared in that instant. Tried it. Wrote it. Said it. Walked in/out. Asked. Answered boldly. Fought for it.
Loved.
Success. Failure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Daring</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/more-daring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 15:56:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/more-daring/</guid>
      <description>Sitting in a Starbucks, writing this before my battery fails. I&amp;rsquo;ve been learning about vulnerability, and wanting more of it in my life. There&amp;rsquo;s a really great book out called Daring Greatly, by Brene Brown.
In a nutshell, it&amp;rsquo;s about: How the Courage to Be Vulnerable Transforms the Way We Live, Love, Parent and Lead. It&amp;rsquo;s been an eye opener. Thanks to @LisaDJenkins for recommending the book. I wholeheartedly recommend it, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Divorced Man&#39;s Death in Pleasantville</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/a-divorced-mans-death-in-pleasantville/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 15:43:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/a-divorced-mans-death-in-pleasantville/</guid>
      <description>Things are fine until they’re not. For gods sake don’t disrupt. Routines set like cheap glue. The pieces fit. They fit until they don’t. Deviations disrupt. Divorces disrupt. The cracks creep in. Cracks conspire. Pleasantville might crumble. Don’t disrupt.
Apparently the neighbors bore my divorce well. They’re not speaking to me either. Neither are they waving. The waving has altogether stopped, as though deliberate and planned in secret. For gods sake don’t wave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart Phones</title>
      <link>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/heart-phones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talentdmrripley.com/archives/heart-phones/</guid>
      <description>Before, my phone beeped like a soft kiss, a nibble; an embrace from another time zone. Now, just a beep. I miss the kiss.
What do future relationships look like? Not too far back our smart phones evolved, grew beyond their pixels, chips, buttons, and data plan coverage maps. Mobile device morphed into the primary conduit for ongoing emotional exchange, especially so when romance is involved — especially more pronounced when long distance romance is in play.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
